http://www.arkbar.com/about-arkbar/privacy-policy

Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Sign in
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
Case SummariesMember DirectoryFastcaseContact UsHelp/FAQsJOIN
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
Content types
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
Date range
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
HomeFor Attorneys ArkBar DocsArkBar Job BoardArkBar Knowledge HubArkansas Bar Commission on Diversity and InclusionArkansas Courts on eFilingCommitteesElection Information for Spring 2021Ethics Advisory OpinionsGovernanceInaugural Board of TrusteesLegal DirectoriesMember BenefitsMembership ApplicationNominations for AwardsPublicationsRelated EntitiesSectionsSustaining ContributionsVolunteer OpportunitiesYoung Lawyers' SectionFor the Public ARKANSASFINDALAWYERArkBar Lawyers Care EventsDiscipline IssuesFor the MediaLaw Related EducationLegal AssistanceLegal LinksMock TrialFrequently Asked QuestionsVoter InformationACE CommitteesSectionsOpen ForumAll CommunitiesMy CommunitiesMy Directory ProfileCLE CLE CENTRAL - Virtual CLE PlatformCLE SearchCLE FAQsCLE MaterialsEvents Sponsorship OpportunitiesEvents CalendarAnnual MeetingMid-Year MeetingPublic Service AcademyHall of FameDirectoryAbout Us Advertising OpportunitiesArkBar Mission and Diversity StatementBar Center LocationFor the MediaHelp/FAQsPayment InformationPhoto GalleryPresident's MessagePrivacy PolicyStaff/Contact UsUser AgreementVendor Assessment FormWebsite TutorialsCOVID-19 Governor's UpdatesLatest UpdatesFree Informational PresentationsVolunteer OpportunitiesCourt ResourcesBusiness ResourcesLocal ExpertsHealth ResourcesVirtual Law Practice Management TipsFun ResourcesArkBar Event UpdatesPractice Link
About UsUser Agreement
User Agreement
License for Association Membership DirectoryApproved by the House of Delegates January 23, 2010All Contents © 2014 Arkansas Bar Association, Inc. All Rights Reserved.The Arkansas Bar Association will license to you the contents of this Directory only if you accept all of the terms and conditions contained in this non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license agreement. Please read this license agreement carefully and accept its terms before using this Member Directory. By opening this Directory, you hereby accept and agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions:This Directory shall be used for individual, personal and confidential reference purposes only, and may be used only pursuant to the terms of this license agreement. This Directory and the contents hereof are proprietary products of Arkansas Bar Association. The contents of this Directory may not, in whole or in part, be reproduced, copied, disseminated, entered into a computer database, used as part of or in connection with a mailing list, or otherwise utilized, in any form or manner or by any means, except for the user's individual, personal and confidential reference. Contained herein are the names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, and email addresses of Arkansas Bar Association members as of the printing of this Directory. Their presence in this Directory represents only that these individuals are members in good standing of Arkansas Bar Association. Arkansas Bar Association does not endorse these members and makes no representations, warranties or guarantees as to, and assumes no responsibility for, the products or services provided by these members. Arkansas Bar Association expressly disclaims all liability for damages of any kind arising out of the use or performance of the products or services provided by these members.
Discussion Group Rules, Etiquette and Privacy Policy
Thank you for being part of our community. To ensure the best possible experience for all members, we have established some basic guidelines for participation.
By joining and using this community, you agree that you have read and will follow these rules and guidelines. This is a great medium with which to solicit the advice of your peers, benefit from their experience, and participate in an ongoing conversation. If you have questions, contact Michele Glasgow.
Please take a moment to acquaint yourself with these important guidelines. If you have questions, contact the member services department. In order to preserve a climate that encourages both civil and fruitful dialogue, we reserve the right to suspend or terminate membership in this community for anyone who violate these rules.
The Rules
Do not challenge or attack others. The discussions and comments are meant to stimulate conversation not to create contention. Let others have their say, just as you may.
Do not post commercial messages on any discussion list, resource library entry, or other area where others might see it. Do not post messages intended to solicit for religious, charitable, commercial or political purposes. Commercial messages include notifications of CLE events offered by any entity aside from the Arkansas Bar Association.  Political purposes include supporting, endorsing or opposing any candidate for political office or for any position within the Arkansas Bar Association. Contact people directly with product and service information if you believe it would help them.
All defamatory, abusive, profane, threatening, offensive, or illegal materials are strictly prohibited. Do not post anything that you would not want the world to see or that you would not want anyone to know came from you.  The Arkansas Bar Association cannot be sure that your post will not be forwarded or printed and shared with others.
No posts shall be made in an attempt to gather support for or against any bill or proposed legislative initiative, whether actually pending or not, aside from legislation which is approved as part of the Arkansas Bar Association Legislative Package.  However, posts regarding feedback requests on propose bills from the Arkansas Bar Association Legislation Committee will be permitted.  Listserv posts are not the official position of the Arkansas Bar Association.
Please note carefully all items listed in the disclaimer and legal rules below, particularly regarding the copyright ownership of information posted.
Remember that other participants have the right to reproduce postings to this site unless you specify otherwise.
Post your message or documents only to the most appropriate lists or libraries. Do not spam several lists or libraries with the same message.
All messages must add to the body of knowledge. We reserve the right to reject any message for any reason.
Discussion Group Etiquette
Include a signature tag on all messages. Include your name, affiliation, location.
State concisely and clearly the topic of your comments in the subject line. This allows members to respond more appropriately to your posting and makes it easier for members to search the archives by subject.
Include only the relevant portions of the original message in your reply. Delete any header information, and put your response before the original posting.
Only send a message to the entire list when it contains information that everyone can benefit from.
Send messages such as "thanks for the information" or "me, too" to individuals--not to the entire list. Do this by using the "Reply to Sender" link to the left of every message.
Do not send administrative messages, such as remove me from the list. Instead, use the web interface to change your settings or to remove yourself from a list. If you are changing e-mail addresses, you do not need to remove yourself from the list and rejoin under your new e-mail address. Simply change your settings.
Warn other list subscribers of lengthy messages either in the subject line or at the beginning of the message body with a line that says "Long Message."
Legal Information
This site is provided as a service for the members of the Arkansas Bar Association.  The Arkansas Bar Association is not responsible for the opinions and information posted on this site by others. We disclaim all warranties with regard to information posted on this site, whether posted by the Arkansas Bar Association or any third party; this disclaimer includes all implied warranties of merchantability and fitness. In no event shall the Arkansas Bar Association be liable for any special, indirect, or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data, or profits, arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of any information posted on this site.
Do not post any defamatory, abusive, profane, threatening, offensive, or illegal materials. Do not post any information or other material protected by copyright without the permission of the copyright owner. By posting material, the posting party warrants and represents that he or she owns the copyright with respect to such material or has received permission from the copyright owner. In addition, the posting party grants the Arkansas Bar Association and users of this site the nonexclusive right and license to display, copy, publish, distribute, transmit, print, and use such information or other material.
Messages should not be posted if they encourage or facilitate members to arrive at any agreement that either expressly or impliedly leads to price fixing, a boycott of another's business, or other conduct intended to illegally restrict free trade. Messages that encourage or facilitate an agreement about the following subjects are inappropriate: prices, discounts, or terms or conditions of sale; salaries; profits, profit margins, or cost data; market shares, sales territories, or markets; allocation of customers or territories; or selection, rejection, or termination of customers or suppliers.
The Arkansas Bar Association does not actively monitor the site for inappropriate postings and does not on its own undertake editorial control of postings. However, in the event that any inappropriate posting is brought to the attention of the Arkansas Bar Association we will take all appropriate action.Prohibited activities include using Arkansas Bar Association forums for any price-fixing, division of markets, and/or other anti-competitive behavior.
The Arkansas Bar Association reserves the right to terminate access to any user who does not abide by these guidelines.
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our organization except as noted below.
With Whom Do We Share the Personal Information We Collect Through This Site
Our Service ProvidersWe may share your personal information with companies (including our affiliates) that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that help process credit card payments. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide specific services on our behalf.Business TransfersYour personal information may be transferred to another entity (either an affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event. If such a transfer were ever to occur, the acquiring entity’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy.Government and Legal DisclosuresWe may disclose the personal information we collect through this Site, when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements that govern your use of this Site; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, or others.
External Sites
We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site (personalization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The InternetWhile we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through our site have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.For any other information please contact us using the Contact Us page.
Connect with us!
Skip Navigation Links
HomeFor AttorneysFor the PublicACECLEEventsDirectoryAbout UsCOVID-19Practice Link
Copyright 2019 Arkansas Bar Association
Powered by Higher Logic
